A Guide to the Governor Timothy M. Kaine, Executive Office-Governor, Records, 2005-2009
Library of Virginia
- II. State Budget Files, 2005-2009., Extent: 5.95 cubic feet (17 boxes). (Box 21-37)
  - 2008 Session
    - Budget Balancing Plan, 9 February 2008 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - The Mid-Session Economic Outlook and Revenue Forecast through Fiscal Year 2010, 11 February 2008 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Cabinet Meeting - 2008-2010 Budget Adjustments, 12 February 2008 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Budget Actions Reports, 17-18 February 2008 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - House Appropriations and Senate Finance Committee, Amendments to HB 29, HB 30 and SB 29, 19 February 2008 (part one) (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - House Appropriations and Senate Finance Committee, Amendments to HB 29, HB 30 and SB 29, 19 February 2008 (part two) (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Budget Meeting, 19 March 2008 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Budget Meeting, 3 April 2008 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Budget Meeting, 7 April 2008 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous Records, 2008 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - 2008 Special Session II (Transportation)
    - 2008 Transportation Special Session (Box 30)
    - Transportation, 2007-2008 (part one) (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Transportation, 2007-2008 (part two) (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - 2009 Pre-Session Budget Materials
    - Report of the Comptroller: A Comprehensive Annual Financial Report for the Fiscal Year Ended June 20, 2008 (Box 30, Volume Volume)
    - Budget Meeting, 26 June 2008 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Budget Meeting, 3 July 2008 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Budget Meeting, 11 July 2008 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Budget Meeting, 12 August 2008 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Budget Records, September 2008 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Budget Meeting, 29 September 2008 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Rail Plan Briefing, 2 October 2008 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - 5, 10 and 15 Percent Budget Reduction Strategies, September/October 2008 (part one) (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - 5, 10 and 15 Percent Budget Reduction Strategies, September/October 2008 (part two) (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Budget Meeting, 4 October 2008 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Budget Meeting, 6 October 2008 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Budget Meeting, 7 October 2008 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - VDOT/CTB, 15 October 2008 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Budget Meetings, 21, 22 and 24 October 2008 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Budget Meetings, 6 November 2008 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Budget Meetings, 7 and 10 November 2008 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Budget Meeting, 12 November 2008 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Supplemental Information for Medicaid/DMAS Budget Reductions and Requests, A briefing for Governor Kaine, 14 November 2008 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Budget Meeting, 17 November 2008 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Budget Meetings, 18, 19, 21, 24 and 25 November 2008 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Budget Meeting, 30 November 2008 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Budget Meeting, 1 December 2008 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Budget Meetings, 3, 4, 5 and 6 December 2008 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Records, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - 2009 Session
    - Budget Bill, 2008-2010 Biennium, House Document No. 1, 17 December 2007 (volume) (Box 33)
    - Budget Bill, 2008-2010 Biennium, House Document No. 1, 17 December 2008 (volume) (Box 33)
    - Budget Documents, 2008-2009 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Budget Documents, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Budget Documents, 2009 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - 2009 Virginia Acts of Assembly, Chapter 781, HB1600, 8 April 2009 (Box 34)
    - American Recovery and Reinvestment Act of 2009 (ARRA) (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - 2010 Pre-Session Budget Materials (2010-2012 Budget Development)
    - Budget Development Documents, May-June 2009 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Budget Development Documents, July-August 2009 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Preliminary Review of Agency Reduction Plans, August 2009 (part one) (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Preliminary Review of Agency Reduction Plans, August 2009 (part two) (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Budget Meeting, 4 August 2009 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates, 5 August 2009 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Budget Meetings, 5 August 2009 - 6 August 2009 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Economic Stimulus Meeting, 17 August 2009 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Budget Meeting, 18 August 2009 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Budget Meeting, 19 August 2009 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Budget Meeting, 21 August 2009 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Budget Meeting, 24 August 2009 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Budget Meeting, 26 August 2009 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Budget Meeting, 30 August 2009 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Budget Meeting, 31 August 2009 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Budget Meeting, 3 September 2009 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Budget Meeting, 4 September 2009 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Talking Points on Addressing the FY2010 Shortfall, 8 September 2009 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Budget Meeting, 14 September 2009 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Budget Meeting, 15 September 2009 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Budget Meeting, 16 September 2009 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Budget Meeting, 18 September 2009 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Budget Meeting, 25 September 2009 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Budget Meeting, 28 September 2009 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Budget Meeting, 30 September 2009 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Budget Meeting, 13 October 2009 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Governor's Advisory Board of Economists, 14 October 2009 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Budget Meeting, 19 October 2009 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Budget Meeting, 29 October 2009 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Budget Meeting, 4 November 2009 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Budget Meeting, 10 November 2009 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Budget Meeting, 11 November 2009 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Budget Meeting, 13 November 2009 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Budget Meeting, 18 November 2009 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Budget Meeting, 20 November 2009 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Budget Meeting, 23 November 2009 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Budget Meeting, 25 November 2009 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates, 23 November 2009 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Budget Meeting, 1 December 2009 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Budget Meeting, 2 December 2009 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Budget Meeting, 4 December 2009 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Budget Meeting, 6 December 2009 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Budget Meeting, 7 December 2009 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Governor Kaine's Remarks to the Joint Money Committees, 18 December 2009 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Budget Bill, SB29, 2008-2010 Biennium, 18 December 2009 (volume) (Box 37)
    - Budget Bill, HB30 and SB30, 2010-2012 Biennium, 18 December 2009 (volume) (Box 37)
- III. Briefing Binders and Reports, 2006-2009., Extent: 2.80 cubic feet (8 boxes). (Box 38-45)
  The Briefing Binders and Reports series is housed in 8 boxes and is arranged chronologically. This series contains briefing binders and reports prepared for Governor Tim Kaine. Briefing Binders include: National Governors Association Winter and Summer meetings, Southern Governors' Association annual meeting, Governor's Advisory Board of Economists (GABE), Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates (GACRE), annual meeting with Virginia's Congressional Delegation and Council on Virginia's Future. The briefing binders usually contain the Governor's itinerary, agendas, background information on attendees, event briefing information, memorandums and reports. Some records include Gov. Kaine's handwritten notes.
  - Governor Kaine's Marketing Trip to Detroit, Michigan, 16 February 2006 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - National Governors Association Winter Meeting, 25 February 2006 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - National Governors Association Winter Meeting, 26 February 2006 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - National Governors Association Winter Meeting, 27 February 2006 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - National Governors Association: Healthy America, 25 February 2006 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - National Governors Association: Education, Early Childhood and Workforce Committee, 27 February 2006 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Hurricane Evacuation and Sheltering Task Force: Report to Governor Timothy M. Kaine, August 2006 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Agency Performance Objectives, 31 August 2006 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Governor's Advisory Board of Economists (GABE) Meeting, 18 October 2006 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Council on Virginia's Future Meeting, 30 October 2006 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates (GACRE) Meeting, 20 November 2006 (part one) (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates (GACRE) Meeting, 20 November 2006 (part two) (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Governor Kaine's Workforce Development Strategic Plan, 28 November 2006 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - The Trip of Governor Timothy M. Kaine and Governor Joe Manchin to Bluefield, Virginia and West Virginia, 30 November 2006 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Report of the Comptroller to the Governor of Virginia for Fiscal Year Ended 30 June 2006, 15 December 2006 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Annual Virginia Congressional Delegation Briefing, 12 February 2007 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - 16th Annual Report on the Performance of State Highway Systems (1984-2005) by Reason Foundation, June 2007 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Southern Governors' Association Annual Meeting, 25-27 August 2007 (part one) (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Southern Governors' Association Annual Meeting, 25-27 August 2007 (part two) (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Energy Plan Briefing Book, July-September 2007 (part one) (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Governor's Energy Plan Briefing Book, July-September 2007 (part two) (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Governor's Energy Plan Briefing Book, July-September 2007 (part three) (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Council on Virginia's Future Meeting, 12 September 2007 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - The Role of At-Risk Funding in Improving Achievement and Opportunity for All Virginia Students, Presentation to the Senate Finance Committee by Dr. Billy K. Cannaday, Jr., Superintendent of Public Instruction, 16 October 2007 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Governor's Advisory Board of Economists (GABE) Meeting, 17 October 2007 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates (GACRE) Meeting, 19 November 2007 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Metropolitan Washington Airports Authority, Dulles Corridor Metro rail Project-Extension to Wiehle Avenue, Supplemental Information and Updates to the Final Design Application, 1 February 2008 (part one) (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Metropolitan Washington Airports Authority, Dulles Corridor Metro rail Project-Extension to Wiehle Avenue, Supplemental Information and Updates to the Final Design Application, 1 February 2008 (part two) (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Metropolitan Washington Airports Authority, Dulles Corridor Metro rail Project-Extension to Wiehle Avenue, Supplemental Information and Updates to the Final Design Application, 1 February 2008 (part three) (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Metropolitan Washington Airports Authority, Dulles Corridor Metro rail Project-Extension to Wiehle Avenue, Supplemental Information and Updates to the Final Design Application, 1 February 2008 (part four) (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Annual Virginia Congressional Delegation Briefing, 4 February 2008 (part one) (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Annual Virginia Congressional Delegation Briefing, 4 February 2008 (part two) (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Annual Virginia Congressional Delegation Briefing, 4 February 2008 (part three) (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - National Governors Association Winter Meeting, 23 February 2008 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - National Governors Association Winter Meeting, 24 February 2008 (part one) (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - National Governors Association Winter Meeting, 24 February 2008 (part two) (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - National Governors Association Winter Meeting, 25 February 2008 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Governor Kaine's Marketing Trip to California (Bay Area, Los Angeles and San Diego), 17-19 June 2008 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - National Governors Association Summer Meeting, 12 July 2008 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Southern Governors' Association Annual Meeting, 8-11 August 2008 (part one) (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Southern Governors' Association Annual Meeting, 8-11 August 2008 (part two) (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Governor's Advisory Board of Economists (GABE) Meeting, 10 September 2008 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - National Capital Region Leaders Meeting (Virginia-Maryland-District of Columbia), 12 September 2008 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - MD/DC/VA Regional Summit, Public Safety Briefing Packet, 12 September 2008 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Governor's Advisory Council on Revenue Estimates (GACRE) Meeting, 23 September 2008 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - SGA Relationship to Council of State Governments: Historical, Administrative, Financial and Mission Considerations, Briefing Materials, 8 October 2008 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Dept. of Taxation, Tax-Related Revenue Raisers Suggestions for the Increase of Revenue in FY09 and FY10, 10 November 2008 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Council on Virginia's Future Meeting, 24 November 2008 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - National Governors Association Winter Meeting, 21-23 February 2009 (part one) (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - National Governors Association Winter Meeting, 21-23 February 2009 (part two) (Box 45, Folder 2)